UTU Additional Collective Bargaining Agreements 6055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UTU Additional Collective Bargaining Agreements
1923-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United Transportaion Union (UTU)
6055
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records.
5771331
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; Arbitration, Industrial; United Transportation Union.
5771331
- A - Delaware (Box 1)
  - Buffalo Creek Railroad Company, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Canadian National Railway Co. Steam Lines Atlantic and Central Regions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Canadian N'l Railways -Prairie and Mountain Regions, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Canadian Pacific Railway Co., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Central of Georgia Railway Co., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Burlington & Quincy Railroad Co., 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul & Pacific Railroad Co., 1938-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Railroad Co., 1956-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chicago, St Paul, Minneapolis & Omaha Railway Co., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland Cincinnati Chicago & St. Louis, 1948-1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clinchfield, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Colorado Fuel & Iron (Steel Corp.), 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Colorado & Southern, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Columbus & Greenville Railway Co., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cumberland Railway & Coal, 1941-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cuyahoga Valley, 1958-1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Davenport Rock Island & North Western, 1957-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Delaward & Hudson, 1953-1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Delaware, Lackawanna & Western, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Denver - Grand Trunk Western (Box 2)
  - Denver & Rio Grande Western, 1943-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Detroit & Toledo Shore Line, 1949-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Detroit Terminal, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Detroit Toledo & Ironton, 1949-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Duluth Missabe & Iron Range, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Duluth, South Shore & Atlantic, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Elgin Joliet & Eastern, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Erie Lackawanna, 1948-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Erie Railroad, 1941-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Florida East Coast, 1946-1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Forth Worth & Denver, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Galveston Wharves, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Georgia, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Grand Trunk Western, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Great Northern - I (Box 3)
  - Great Northern Rwy. (Folder 1 of 2), 1944-1957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Great Northern Rwy. (Folder 2 of 2), 1943-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Movile & Ohio, 1955-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Houston Belt & Terminal, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Green Bay & Western (Folder 1 of 2), 1952-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Green Bay & Western (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Central, 1954-1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Illinois Terminal, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Indiana Harbor Belt, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Indianapolis Union, 1951-1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- J - Los Angeles (Box 4)
  - Jacksonville Terminal, 1927-1935 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Joint Texas Div. of CRI&P And FW&D, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kansas City Southern, 1949-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kansas City Terminal, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1940-1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kennecott Copper Corporation (Folder 2 of 2), 1962-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kentucky & Indiana Terminal, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lake Terminal, 1961-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lancaster & Chester, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Lehigh & Hudson River, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Lehigh & New England, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Lehigh Valley, 1954-1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Junction, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Long Island, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Louisiana - M (Box 5)
  - Manufacturers, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Louisiana & Arkansas Rwy., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Louisville & Nashville, 1950-1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - MC Keesport Connecting, 1943-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Minneapolis & St. Louis, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Maine Central, 1942-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault STE. Marie (Later to Become the Soo Line), 1946-1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Minnesota Dakota & Western, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    Agreement btwn. Minnesota Dakota & Western Railway Company and United Transportation Union (Trainmen)
  - Modesto & Empire Traction Co., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Monessen Soithwestern Rwy. Co., 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Monongahela Connecting, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Missouri Illinois, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Missouri - Kansas -Texas, 1953-1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Missouri Pacific, 1946-1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- N - New York (Box 6)
  - Nashville Chattanooga & St. Louis, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New Orleans Public Belt, 1953-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - New York Central-- Eastern Dist., 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New York Central-- Northern Distric, 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - New York Central System, 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - New York Central--Western Dist., 1937-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New York, Chicago & St. Louis (Nickel Plate Road), 1953-1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New York New Haven & Hartford, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Newburgh - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 7)
  - Newburgh & South Shore, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern Pacific R.R., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Norfolk and Western, 1954-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Northern Pacific, 1954-1957 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ogden Union RY & Depot, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pacific Electric Harbor Belt Line, 1943-1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Penn Central _ Eastern District, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania RR., 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Pacific Great Eastern, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Patapsco & Bank Rivers, 1956-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge - R (Box 8)
  - Phelps Dodge, 1950-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia Bethlehem & New England, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh & Lake Erie, 1946-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Pittsburgh & Ohio Valley, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh & West Virginia RWY., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Pittsburgh Chartiers & Yocghiogheny, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Port Terminal RR Assn - Texas, 1958-1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Portland Terminal, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Quanah, Acme & Pacific RWY. Co., 1962 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Quebec North Shore & Labrador, 1962-1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Collective Agreement employed by the Railway Booklet- in English and French
  - Reading, 1953-1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - River Terminal, 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Robeling Sons-John A., 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- S - Southern Pacific, Pacific System I (Box 9)
  - St. Louis San Francisco, 1953-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis S, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Seaboard Coast Line, 1940-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Seaboard Coast Line II, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Seaboard Coast Line, 1959-1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Shaker Heights Rapid Transit -- BLE, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Soo Line (Formerly Known As Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie), 1955 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - South Buffalo, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Southern Pacific- Pacific System I, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Southern Pacific, Pacific System II - Texas Pacific (Box 10)
  - Southern Pacific- Pacific System II, 1955-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Southern Pacific --T&L Lines Part I, 1962-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Southern Pacific --T&L Lines Part II, 1953-1959 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Southern Railway, 1923-1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Staten Island Rapid Transit Rwy., 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Steelton & Highspire, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sydney & Louisburg, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Tacoma Municipal Belt Line, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Terminal R.R. Association of St. Louis, 1930-1944 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Texas & Pacific, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Texas Pacific- Missouri Pacific Term. Railroad of New Orleans, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Toledo - Z (Box 11)
  - Toledo Peoria & Western, 1954-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Toledo Terminal, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Union Carbide Corp., Mining & Metals DIV., 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Union Pacific--Central District, 1952-1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Union Pacific -- Eastern District, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Union Pacific --Southwest District, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Union Railroad (Pittsburgh), 1941-1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Union Terminal, 1958-1976 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Virginian Rwy., 1946 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Wabash, 1942-1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Western Maryland, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Western Pacific, 1953-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Wheeling & Lake Erie, 1937-1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Youngstown & Northern R.R. Co., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)